export const data = [
  {
    id: '1',
    question: 'What is 2 + 2?',
    options: ['2', '4', '6', '8'],
    correctAnswer: '4',
  },
  {
    id: '2',
    question: 'What is 3 + 3?',
    options: ['4', '6', '8', '10'],
    correctAnswer: '6',
  },
  {
    id: '3',
    question: 'What is 4 + 4?',
    options: ['6', '8', '10', '12'],
    correctAnswer: '8',
  },
  {
    id: '4',
    question: 'What is 5 + 5?',
    options: ['10', '15', '20', '25'],
    correctAnswer: '10',
  },
  {
    id: '5',
    question: 'What is 6 + 6?',
    options: ['12', '18', '24', '30'],
    correctAnswer: '12',
  },
  {
    id: '6',
    question: 'What is 7 + 7?',
    options: ['14', '21', '28', '35'],
    correctAnswer: '14',
  },
  {
    id: '7',
    question: 'What is 8 + 8?',
    options: ['16', '24', '32', '40'],
    correctAnswer: '16',
  },
  {
    id: '8',
    question: 'What is 9 + 9?',
    options: ['18', '27', '36', '45'],
    correctAnswer: '18',
  },
  {
    id: '9',
    question: 'What is 10 + 10?',
    options: ['20', '30', '40', '50'],
    correctAnswer: '20',
  },
  {
    id: '10',
    question: 'What is 11 + 11?',
    options: ['22', '33', '44', '55'],
    correctAnswer: '22',
  },
]
